// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answer
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which of the following states of India does not share a boundary with Myanmar?",
        answer: "Assam",
        options: ["Arunachal Pradesh",
            "Manipur",
            "Nagaland",
            "Assam"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "The water comes to Indira Gandhi Canal from the following Rivers?",
        answer: "Sutlej & Bea",
        options: ["Sutlej Only",
            "Sutlej & Beas",
            "Sutlej, Beas & Ravi",
            "Sutlej, Beas , Ravi & Chenab"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "In which of the following Mahi River falls?",
        answer: "Gulf of Khambat",
        options: ["Gulf of Kachchh",
            "Ranna of Kachchh",
            "Gulf of Khambat",
            "Gulf of Munnar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which of the following represents largest fraction of forest cover in India?",
        answer: "Tropical moist Deciduous",
        options: ["Tropical Dry deciduous",
            "Tropical moist Deciduous",
            "Tropical Evergreen",
            "Sub tropical"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Pagladia Dam Project is located in which state?",
        answer: "Assam",
        options: ["Arunachal Pradesh",
            "Sikkim",
            "Assam",
            "West Bengal"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which of the following is the northern most point of India?",
        answer: "Indira Col",
        options: ["Cape Camorin",
            "Indira Col",
        	"Guhar Moti",
            "Pigmalion Point"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the rank of India In terms of the total area?",
        answer: "7th",
        options: ["3rd",
            "5th",
            "7th",
            "10th"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "The deep ravined and gullies cut by the Chambal river in the Malwa plateau is known as by which of the following name?",
        answer: "Badland",
        options: ["Barkhans",
            "Badland",
            "Maidan",
            "Hamada"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which among the following statements are correct? <br> 1.	Coromandel coast formed due to emergence <br> 2.	Malabar coast formed due to emergence <br> 3.	Konkan coast formed due to submergence <br> Choose the correct option from the codes given below: ",
        answer: "1, 2 & 3",
        options: ["1 & 2",
            "1 & 3",
            "2 & 3",
            "1, 2 & 3"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "With which of the following countries of South East Asia, India shares a maritime boundary?",
        answer: "Indonesia",
        options: ["Indonesia",
            "Malaysia",
            "Singapore",
            "Vietnam"
        ]
    }
]